Guide to the Tobacco Collection, 1828-1987 and undated, bulk 1870-1955 RL.01300
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Listing of Items By Company Name
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): Military medal] (Box 3)
    Iron Cross.
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): National flags], 18 items (Box 3)
    Incl. British North Borneo, Papal State, and Trieste.
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): National seals], 2 items (Box 3)
    Egypt and Germany.
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): Pennants (colleges)], 4 items (Box 3)
    Indiana, Northwestern, Rochester, and St. Louis.
  - Unknown, New England Yacht Club [Fabric Inserts (silks): Pennants (yacht clubs)] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): National flags, songs & flowers series], 19 items (Box 3)
    Incl. Austria-Hungary, Servia, Wales, and Zion.
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): Flags ], 13 items (Box 2)
    Small silks.
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): Coat of arms], 2 items (Box 2)
    Small silks. Russia and the Netherlands.
  - Unknown, (2 items) (1 Tokio cigarettes) [Fabric Inserts (silks): Butterflies] (Box 2)
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): Birds], 2 items (Box 2)
    Small silks. Canadian Warbler and the Wood Duck.
  - Unknown, Olga, Queen of Greece [Fabric Inserts (silks): Royals] (Box 2)
  - Unknown, Nebo Cigarettes [Fabric Inserts (silks): Berries] (Box 2)
  - Unknown, Piedmont [Insert Cards: Fish Series (1 to 50)], 37 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Sweet Caporal Cigarettes[Insert Cards: Fish Series (1 to 100)], 53 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Recruit Little Cigars [Insert Cards: flags of all nations series], 61 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Recruit Little Cigars [Insert Cards: types of nations series], 17 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Various Brands [Insert Cards: types of all nations series], 19 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Souvenir program, national tobacco festival [Pamphlet] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Unknown, Tobacco Leaves [Pamphlet: Berlyn, Felix S.], 1909 (Box 3)
    1909 Christmas number.
  - Unknown, Almanac [Pamphlet: Bonitz, Julius A.], 1883 (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Dr. M.L. Byrn's Medical Cabinet [Pamphlet: Byrn, M. Lafayette], 1861 (Box 3)
  - Unknown, From the Plant Bed to Market [Pamphlet: Ragland, Robert L.], 1879 (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Tobacco Seed Circular [Pamphlet: Ragland, Robert L.], 1882 (Box 3)
  - Unknown, "British Mixture" [Pamphlet: Whitman, E.B.], 1883 (Box 3)
    Investors' Trust, No. 15.
  - Unknown, Castle Hall Twin Cigars [Poster] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Nickel Movement Cigars [Poster] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Orange Flower Cigar [Poster] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, "Three Maids" Cigar [Poster] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Good Times/Honey Dew [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Unknown, Stolen Kisses [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Unknown, Tiger Brand [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Unknown, _____ Trademark [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Unknown, Ten Pounds Stamps: Nos. A 120563, 120565, and 120568 [Tobacco Stamps, U.S. Internal Revenue, First Series], 3 items (Box 3)
    Re-issue authorized by Act of June 6 1872, & cancelled with new steel die required by that Act, for use by manufacturers of plug and fine-cut chewing tobacco, & issued Sept. 30, 1873, by collector of 6th District, N.C., County Line, Davie County, N.C., & cancelled Oct. 1, 1873.
  - Unknown, Forty Pounds Stamps: Nos. A 294794 and 327216 [Tobacco Stamps, U.S. Internal Revenue, First Series], 2 items (Box 3)
    Re-issue authorized by Act of June 6 1872, & cancelled with new steel die required by that Act, for use by manufacturers of plug and fine-cut chewing tobacco, & issued Sept. 30, 1873, by collector of 6th District, N.C., County Line, Davie County,
  - Unknown, Regie Francaise (Sultanes) [Trade Cards: foreign] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Regie Francaise (Gitanes) [Trade Cards: foreign] (Box 3)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., "The Famous Dukes" [Poster (framed)] (Box 7)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Cross Cut Cigarettes [Poster], 2 items (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Fancy Dress Ball Costumes [Poster] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Honest Long Cut [Poster] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Honest Long Cut [Poster] (Oversize-folder 2)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Mail [Poster] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Shadows [Poster] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., 250 Most Beautiful Women of the World [Poster] (Oversize-folder 2)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Circus Entertainers [Trade Cards], 2 items (Box 6)
    Durham, N.C. (Miss Mulvey and an Acrobat).
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Actresses (Mounted) [Trade Cards] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Tobacco Advertising & W. Duke & Sons. [Slides (35 mm.)], 2 items (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Cross-Cut Cigarettes [Broadside] (Box 6)
    Durham, N.C. (Pasted on back of a painting signed DORSE, dated 1904).
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Fatima Cigarette Package Reproduced [Envelope] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., Fatima Turkish Blend Cigarettes [Envelope] (Box 6)
  - W. Duke, Sons & Co., To the Public [Poster] (Box 6)
  - W.H. Coe Mf'g. Co., Gold Leaf [Cans], 4 items (Box 4)
    Providence, R.I.
  - W.L. Venable & Co., Carolina Belle Scotch Snuff [Trade Card] (Box 2)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham General Store [Poster] (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Durham [Labels], 14 items (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham [Envelope] (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Durham [Wrappers], 2 items (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., "Durham Whifs" no.1, vol.1 [Pamphlet] (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Blackwell's Durham [Coupon] (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Durham Tobacco [Envelope] (Box 6)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Blackwell's Durham Clear Havana [Cigar Box] (Box 4)
  - W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham [Tobacco Pouch with Rolling Papers] (Box 4)
  - W.W. Russell, Leopard Tobacco [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Waldorf-Astoria Segar Co., The Waldorf Cigarros [Cigar Band ] (Box 2)
  - Watson & McGill, Black Swan [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, Britannica [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, Crusader [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, The Enchanter [Poster], 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, Grand National [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, Harlequin [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, The International [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, MacRae Fine Tobacco [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Watson & McGill, Triumph [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Wm. Cameron & Bro., Courage [Posters], 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Y. Pendas & Alvarez, Webster [Cigar Box Label] (Box 1)
    Fragile: handle with care.
- Listing By Format
  - Album: insert cards, Unknown, Various British companies, 188 cards (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, R.J. Reynolds, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Blotter,"44" Cigar Company, 44 Cigars (Lipschutz) (Box 1)
  - Book, National Cigar Co., Private Label Cigars (Box 1)
  - Book: Cruse, Alfred J., Unknown, All About Cigarette Cards (Box 2)
  - Book, New York Cigar, Specimens of Cigar Box Labels (Box 1)
  - Booklet: cigarette papers, Unknown, New Size, New Kind (Box 2)
  - Booklet, Gonzalez & Sanchez, Havana Cigars (Box 1)
  - Booklet, La Reclama Cuban Factory, Smokers Guide (Box 2)
  - Booklet, John Slater & Co., Smokers' Guide (For Men Only) "Slater's Stogies" (Box 2)
  - Broadside, Roth, Brunner & Feist, Old Glory & War Eagle Cheroots (Box 2)
    Cincinnati, Ohio (L. Richardson Drug Co., Greensboro N.C.).
  - Broadside, Simpson & Smith, The "Gem Segar Pipe" (Box 2)
  - Broadside, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Cross-Cut Cigarettes (Box 6)
  - Broadside, Harris & Flippen, Tobacco Barn Flues, 1885 June (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Lea & Noell, Leaf Tobacco (Box 1)
  - Broadside, The Mammoth Tobacco Co., Notice "Winston's Best" Tobacco (Box 1)
  - Broadside, R.F. Morris & Son M'f'g. Co., "Our Key Unlocks the Door!" (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Moss, Birdsong & Co., Farmers Warehouse (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, Pace's (Brick) Warehouse (Box 1)
  - Broadside, La Reclama Cuban Factory, La Reclama Examiner (Box 2)
  - Broadside, Liipfert, Scales & Co., Save Liipfert, Scales & Co.'s Tags and Bags, 1900 (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Interstate Tobacco- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best, 1947 Apr. 15 (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Interstate Tobacco- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best, 1947 May 26 (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Interstate Tobacco- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best, 1947 June 23 (Box 1)
  - Broadside, Interstate Tobacco- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best, 1947 July 8 (Box 1)
  - Brochure, Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, "Steer for Pace's Warehouse,"1882 (Box 1)
  - Brochure, R.J. Reynolds, Whitaker Park (Box 2)
  - Cans, W.H. Coe Mf'g. Co., Gold Leaf, 4 items (Box 4)
    Providence, RI.
  - Catalog, Nat Sherman (tobacconist), Sherman's (Box 2)
  - Catalog, R.A. Patterson & Co., 6th Annual Descriptive Catalogue, 1885 (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box, Ignacio Haya, Panetela Genade (Gold Label) (Cigar-box 1-2)
  - Cigar Band, Waldorf-Astoria Segar Co., The Waldorf Cigarros (Box 2)
  - Cigar Band, Jamaica Tobacco Co., Ltd., Royal Jamaica, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Blackwell's Durham Clear Havana (Box 4)
  - Cigar Box Cover, American Tobacco Company, Victory, 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cigar Box Label, Manuel Garcia Alonso, Undesignated (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Krueger & Brown, Author of Waverly, 2 items (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Krueger & Brown, Bella Primera, 2 items (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Krueger & Brown, Bonita Signora (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Krueger & Brown, Royal Life, 2 items (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Krueger & Brown, Undesignated, 4 items (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Y. Pendas & Alvarez, Webster (Box 1)
  - Cigar Box Label, Toro y Compania, Sociedad en Comandita, El Toro de la Selva Tabacos (Box 2)
  - Cigar Box Labels, Unknown, Cigarros Exquisitos, 3 items (Box 2)
  - Cigar Box Labels, Unknown, Habana (Box 2)
  - Cigar Box Labels, Unknown, Undesignated Brand, 4 items (Box 2)
  - Cigar Box Labels, Unknown, Kohler's Handmade, 4 items (Box 2)
  - Cigar Box Labels, Unknown, Dick Custer, 2 items (Box 2)
  - Cigar Box, American Cigar Co., Division of American Brands. Antonio y Cleopatra Grenadiers (Cigar-box 1-2)
  - Cigar Box, T.E. Brooks & Co., El-Rees-So (Cigar-box 1-2)
  - Cigar Box, Consolidated Cigar Corporation., Dutch Masters Perfecto (Cigar-box 1-2)
  - Cigar Box, Havatampa Cigar Co., Hav-a-Tampa, 3 items (Cigar-box 1-2)
  - Cigarette Case, Camel (Box 4)
    Typical of those distributed at Duke football games.
  - Cigar Wrapper, Krueger & Brown, Author of Waverly (Box 1)
  - Cigar Wrapper, Krueger & Brown, Bella Primera, 2 items (Box 1)
  - Cigar Wrapper, Krueger & Brown, Royal Life (Box 1)
  - Clipping, American Tobacco Company, Sovereign Cigarettes (Box 5)
    Enquirer Sun, Columbus, Ga.
  - Clippings (Copies), P. Lorillard, Old Gold Advertisement, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
    Jersey City, NJ. (The Chronicle).
  - Clippings: Le Figaro, Unknown, "La Decouverte des Cigars" (Box 6)
  - Coupon, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Blackwell's Durham (Box 6)
  - Coupons, Schulte Cigar Co., 4 items (Box 2)
  - Envelope, Boston Cigar & Tobacco Co., Poet Cigars (William Cullen Bryant) (Box 1)
  - Envelope, F.R. Durgin, Flying Dude Cigar (Box 1)
  - Envelope, Holmes & Miller Plug & Twist Tobacco, ca. 189__ (Box 1)
  - Envelope, E.V. Schnoor Cigar Co, Mapacuba Cigars (Box 2)
  - Envelope, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham (Box 6)
  - Envelope, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Durham Tobacco (Box 6)
  - Envelope, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Fatima Cigarette Package Reproduced (Box 6)
  - Envelope, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Fatima Turkish Blend Cigarettes (Box 6)
  - Envelope, Liipfert, Scales & Co., School Boy & National Chew, 1900 August 11 (Box 1)
  - Envelope, A. Ralph & Co., Snuff, 1870 Oct. 8 (Box 2)
  - Envelopes, Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, 1883 March 8 and n.d., 2 items (Box 1)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): flags of america, Unknown, 13 Flags of America (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): flags of america, Unknown, 6 Flags of America with Arms (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flag with no emblem, Unknown, United States (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 21 items (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 35 items (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with decorated squares in corners (no emblems), Unknown, Corea (Korea) (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with decorated squares in corners (no emblems), Unknown, Panama (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with corner emblems (no squares), Unknown, Hayti (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with corner emblems (no squares), Unknown, Union Jack (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with corner emblems (no squares), Unknown, United States (Beige background) (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with corner emblems (no squares), Unknown, United States (Green background) (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with emblem in squares in corners, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 5 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with emblem in squares in corners, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 14 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with emblem in squares in corners, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 3 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 3 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (flannel): national flags with decorated squares in corners (no emblems), Unknown, Turkey-Egypt (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (Plush, Fringed Ends) rugs, Unknown, No Brand Designation (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (Plush, Fringed Ends) rugs, Unknown, No Brand Designation (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): flags, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 13 items (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Coat of arms, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 2 items (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Butterflies, Unknown, 2 items; 1 Tokio cigarettes (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Birds, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 2 items (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Royals, Unknown, Olga, Queen of Greece (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Berries, Unknown, Nebo Cigarettes (Box 2)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): college seal, Unknown, No Brand Designation (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Military medals, Unknown, No Brand Designation (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): National flags, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 18 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): National seal, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 2 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Pennants (college), Unknown, No Brand Designation, 4 items (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): Pennants (yacht club), Unknown, New England Yacht Club (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts (silks): National flag, song & flowers series, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 19 items (Box 3)
    Incl. Austria-Hungary, Serbia, Wales, and Zion.
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, U.S. Naval Academy (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, Brown--Baseball (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, Columbia--Hammer Throw, Hurdles, and Rowing (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, Georgetown--Hockey and Hurdles (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, Princeton--Hammer Throw and Hockey (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, Stanford--Rowing (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, Syracuse--Golf (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series, Unknown, U.S. Military Academy (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: National flags, songs & flowers series, Unknown, Germany (Box 3)
  - Fabric Inserts: National flags series, Unknown, No Brand Designation, 2 items (Box 3)
  - Financial Statements, R.J. Reynolds, 1920, 1927-1932, 7 items (Box 2)
  - Insert, A. Ralph & Co., Ralph's Carolina Snuff (Box 2)
  - Insert Cards, Alexander Boguslavsky, Ltd., Turf (Conan Doyle Characters), 25 items (Box 1)
  - Insert Cards: fish series (1 to 50), Unknown, Piedmont, 37 items (Box 3)
  - Insert Cards: Fish Series (1 to 100), Unknown, Sweet Caporal Cigarettes, 53 items (Box 3)
  - Insert Cards: Flags of all nations series, Unknown, Recruit Little Cigars, 61 items (Box 3)
  - Insert Cards: Types of nations series, Unknown, Recruit Little Cigars, 17 items (Box 3)
  - Insert Cards: Types of all nations series, Unknown, Various Brands, 19 items (Box 3)
  - Insert Cards, John Player & Sons, Players Cigarettes, 50 items (Box 1)
  - Insert Cards, John Player & Sons, Players Cigarettes, 50 items (Box 1)
  - Insert Cards, Allen and Ginter, Birds of America, Snow Bird (Box 5)
  - Insert Cards, S. Anargyrus, Turkish Trophies, 24 items (Box 6)
  - Label (Cigar Box), José Alonso y Ca. (Box 1)
  - Label, J.H. McElwee, Ante-Bellum Smoking Tobacco (Box 1)
  - Label, Jacob G. Shirk, Homestead (Box 2)
  - Label, R.L. Swain Tobacco Co., Pinehurst Cigarettes (Box 2)
  - Labels, Fabrica de Tabacos, Cigar Box (Undesignated) (Box 1)
  - Label, Fabrica de Tabacos, La Vencedora (Box 1)
  - Label, Fabrica de Tabacos, La Esprecion (Box 1)
  - Labels, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Durham, 14 items (Box 6)
  - Leaflet, Gebruder Blum, Auswalt billiger Sorten (Box 1)
  - Leaflet, Click-Rierson Co., "Reference and Responsibility" (Box 1)
  - Leaflet, New York & Havana Cigar Co., "Descriptive Price List" (Box 1)
  - Leaflet, La Reclama Cuban Factory, La Reclama Cigar (Box 2)
  - Leaflet, J.W. Roberts & Son, Get Your Cigars Direct from "The Havana of America" (Box 2)
  - Letter, Holmes & Miller Plug & Twist Tobacco, 189__ (Signed Laura) (Box 1)
  - Letter, La Reclama Cuban Factory, La Reclama Cigar (Box 1)
  - Letter, Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, Signed A.B.G., 1883 March 8 (Box 1)
  - Letter, A. Ralph & Co., Ralph's Carolina Snuff, 1870 Sept. 15 (Box 2)
  - Night letter (Telegram), W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham (with purchase of 25# a box of "Cork" soap) (Box 6)
  - Pamphlet (Tobaccoland Magazine), Liggett & Myers, Liggett Group (Oversize-box 22)
  - Pamphlet: Bonitz, Julius A., Unknown, Almanac, 1883 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet, Ragland, Robert L., Unknown, From the Plant Bed to Market, 1879 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet, Ragland, Robert L., Unknown, Tobacco Seed Circular, 1882 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet, Whitman, E.B., Unknown, "British Mixture", 1883 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet: national tobacco festival, Unknown, Souvenir Program (Oversize-box 22)
  - Pamphlet: Berlyn, Felix S., Unknown, Tobacco Leaves, 1909 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet, Byrn, M. Lafayette, Unknown, Dr. M.L. Byrn's Medical Cabinet, 1861 (Box 3)
  - Pamphlet, Liggett & Myers, Bridge by Ely Culbertson, 1936 Play and Scoring (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet, W.T. Blackwell & Co., "Durham Whifs" no. 1, vol. 1 (Box 6)
  - Pamphlet, James G. Tinsley & Co., Fertilizers for Tobacco, 1889 (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet, Brown's Ware House, Moseley R.D. Brown's, Alpha-Beti-Cal Advertiser, 1877 (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet, EE-M Co., "EE-M Smoking Tobacco and Cigarettes", 1896 (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet, F.W. Felgner & Sons, Price List of Smoking Tobacco, 1866 Aug. 1 (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet, Hill & Skinner, "To the Planters of Virginia and North Carolina", 1875 (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet, Liggett & Myers, Catalogue of Presents Offered for Tobacco Tags Tobacco Coupons and Cigarette Coupons, 1916 (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet, R.J. Reynolds, Research, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet, R.J. Reynolds, A Short History of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet, Southern Fertilizing Co., The Position Tobacco Has Held as the Chief Source of Wealth to Virginia, 1876 (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet, S.W. Travers & Co., A Few Facts on the Cultivation of Tobacco, 1886 (Box 2)
  - Pamphlet, Ligget & Myers, The New Tobaccoland USA, 1948 (Oversize-box 1)
  - Pamphlet, Liggett & Myers, Tobaccoland USA, 1940, 2 items (Oversize-box 22)
  - Pamphlet, Liggett & Myers, Tobaccoland USA, 1951 (Oversize-box 22)
  - Pamphlet, Liggett & Myers, The Companies of Your Pleasure, 1979 (Box 1)
  - Picture (Framed), Liggett & Myers, Fatima Cigarettes (Oversize-box 22)
  - Picture (Framed), Liggett & Myers, Fatima Cigarettes (Oversize-box 22)
  - Playing Card, Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Hard A Port Cut Plug (Oversize-box 22)
  - Poster (framed), W. Duke, Sons & Co., "The Famous Dukes" (Box 6)
  - Poster, D.S. Erb & Co., La Flor de Erb Cigar (Box 1)
  - Poster, Hill & Fritz, Kangaroo Tobacco (Box 1)
  - Poster, J.W. Stoddard & Co., The Tiger, King of Rakes (Box 2)
  - Poster, Unknown, Castle Hall Twin Cigars (Box 3)
  - Poster, Unknown, Nickel Movement Cigars (Box 3)
  - Poster, Unknown, Orange Flower Cigar (Box 3)
  - Poster, Unknown, "Three Maids" Cigar (Box 3)
  - Poster, P. Lorillard, Dandy Jim (Oversize-box 1)
    Jersey City, NJ.
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., 250 Most Beautiful Women of the World (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Poster, G.W. Gail & Ax of Baltimore, Navy Smoking Tobacco (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, American Indians (Box 5)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, Birds of Tropics (Box 5)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, Editors (Box 5)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, Pirates of the Spanish Main (Box 5)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, Richmond Straight-Cut (Box 5)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, Virginia Brights (Box 5)
  - Poster, Allen and Ginter, World's Smokers (Box 5)
  - Poster, National Tobacco Works, Piper Heidseck Plug Tobacco (Box 5)
  - Poster, American Tobacco Company, Bull Durham, 6 items (Box 5)
  - Poster, S. Anargyrus, Egyptian Deities (Box 6)
  - Poster, W.T. Blackwell & Co., Bull Durham General Store (Box 6)
  - Poster, Buchanan & Lyalls Mf'g., Planet & Neptune Plug Tobacco (Box 6)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Cross Cut Cigarettes, 2 items (Box 6)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Fancy Dress Ball Costumes (Box 6)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Mail (Box 6)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Shadows (Box 6)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., To the Public (Box 6)
  - Poster, Helmar (Turkish Tobacco), Turkish Cigarettes (Box 6)
  - Poster, Kinney Bros., Butterfly Collection (Box 6)
  - Poster, Kinney Bros., Duel After the Ball (Box 6)
  - Poster, D.H. McAlpin Co., Chew Virginia Leaf (Box 6)
  - Poster, National Tobacco Works, Newsboy Plug Tobacco (Box 6)
  - Poster, Harry Weissinger Tobacco Co., Peace & Good Will (Box 6)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Honest Long Cut (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Poster, W. Duke, Sons & Co., Honest Long Cut (Box 6)
  - Poster, British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., Drummond's Horseshoe (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., Cycle Cigarettes (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., Winner Plug Tobacco (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Brown & Williamson, Old North State Cigarette (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Alex'r Cameron & Co., Venus (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, David Dunlop, Belle of Virginia (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, David Dunlop, Columbia (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, David Dunlop, The Derby (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, David Dunlop, Fair Maid (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, David Dunlop, La Plata, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Just the Thing (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Lord Beaconsfield (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Picture of a King (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Red Funnel (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Sailor's Hope, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, Brown & Williamson, Old North State Cigarette (Oversize-box 1)
  - Poster, W.W. Russell, Leopard Tobacco (Oversize-box 1)